{
    "categories": [],
    "description": " Try to guess capital cities of all the countries in Asia. ",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Japan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Beijing",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "China"
    }, {
        "answer": "Seoul",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "South Korea"
    }, {
        "answer": "New Delhi",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "India"
    }, {
        "answer": "Singapore",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Singapore"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kabul",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Afghanistan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jerusalem",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Israel"
    }, {
        "answer": "Manila",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Philippines"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bangkok",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Thailand"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jakarta",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Indonesia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Baghdad",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Iraq"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tehran",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Iran"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kuala Lumpur",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Malaysia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Pyongyang",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "North Korea"
    }, {
        "answer": "Taipei",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Taiwan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Islamabad",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Pakistan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ankara",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Turkey"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kuwait City",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kuwait"
    }, {
        "answer": "Hanoi",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Vietnam"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kathmandu",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Nepal"
    }, {
        "answer": "Abu Dhabi",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "United Arab Emirates"
    }, {
        "answer": "Riyadh",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Saudi Arabia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dhaka",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Bangladesh"
    }, {
        "answer": "Damascus",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Syria"
    }, {
        "answer": "Beirut",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Lebanon"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ulaanbaatar",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Mongolia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Baku",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Azerbaijan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Amman",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Jordan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Nicosia",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Cyprus"
    }, {
        "answer": "Doha",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Qatar"
    }, {
        "answer": "Phnom Penh",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Cambodia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tbilisi",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Georgia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Yerevan",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Armenia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Astana",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kazakhstan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sana'a",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Yemen"
    }, {
        "answer": "Muscat",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Oman"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dili",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "East Timor"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vientiane",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Laos"
    }, {
        "answer": "Mal√©",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Maldives"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tashkent",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Uzbekistan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Manama",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Bahrain"
    }, {
        "answer": "Thimphu",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Bhutan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bandar Seri Begawan",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Brunei"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bishkek",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kyrgyzstan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ashgabat",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Turkmenistan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dushanbe",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Tajikistan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Naypyidaw",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Burma"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte",
        "category": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Sri Lanka"
    }],
    "quizLength": 48,
    "title": "Asia Capitals Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/asian-capitals-quiz.php"
}